Yaga, what is that thing?
It is possible to have
man-made cursed corpses
act more autonomously than
other forms of manipulation.
But they're always powered by
consuming cursed energy
from the sorcerer.
Yet that thing is sustaining
itself on its own cursed energy.
The higher-ups are currently trying
to designate you as a special-grade
and officially sentence you
to indefinite imprisonment.
Because if you can intentionally
create that thing,
you could easily have your own army.
Answer me, Yaga.
Do you truly not know how
that thing was made?
Correct.
Masamichi.
Everyone's worried about you.
They say you seem down.
I see.
So I told them all this!
If you're feeling down,
we just have to cheer you up!
That so?
I'm a genius, aren't I?
Yeah.
Takeru, I'm sorry, but I won't be
able to come home for a while.
Please let the others know, too.
Leaving for work again?
Yeah. It'll be a long trip.
Don't worry.
This forest is protected by Tengen-sama.
Your mother will come see you again, too.
You'll be all right without me.
Masamichi.
It'll be lonely without you, Masamichi.
Are you sure, Kusakabe?
Don't go telling anyone I helped you.
You were captured to lure Yaga-san out.
And I owe that man a favor.
Go on, get!
You're really sure about this?
This thing is not your nephew.
It's just something with
your nephew's information.
You're trying to tell me
I can't live in the present
if I stay hung up on the
dead forever, right?
Still...
My little sister can no longer
live without Takeru.
Masamichi, that lady's
my mother, isn't she?
Yeah. Good job recognizing her.
I had a feeling it was her.
I'm a genius, aren't I?
Takeru!
I'm sorry, but...
I know.
You can't let the existence of your fully
autonomous cursed corpses become known.
So he can't live with her.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Thanks a lot.
I mean it.
Thank you.
Where do you think you're going without
any cursed corpses, Principal Yaga?
To see my son.
Since you've been sentenced to death,
allow me to tell you the
one way to save your life.
Disclose how you create those fully
autonomous man-made cursed corpses!
You all sure grew bold the
moment Satoru was gone.
Principal.
I'll handle the rest, so you may leave.
Understood.
You use the body's information to
reproduce the soul's information.
Then you place that soul information
in the cursed corpse's core.
That's not enough, though.
You have to place cores housing
three highly compatible souls
into a single cursed corpse,
and make those souls observe
each other at all times.
Doing that
finally allows the souls to stabilize
so self-awareness can take root.
Roughly three months after that's born,
it will begin supplying
its own cursed energy.
Why?!
Why share that now?!
Why wouldn't you reveal that sooner?!
Why didn't you try to live longer?!
Because...
it's a curse, Principal Gakuganji.
A curse from me to you.
Masamichi!
Why don't you fight?
Do you not hate me?
Pandas aren't bound by things like that.
Besides, you were never on
bad terms with Masamichi.
To me, you're just the
knife that fell upon him.
Just make sure you remember this...
Even pandas cry.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Kinji Hakari is currently earning money
as a bookie for a fight club he's running
in an abandoned multi-story
parking garage in Tochigi Prefecture.
A fight club?
They host fist fights between sorcerers.
Then the spectators are...
Generally non-sorcerers.
That blatantly violates the secrecy
mandated in Article 8 of the Jujutsu Code.
ARTICLE 8 - SECRECY: SORCERERS MUST NOT
REVEAL THE EXISTENCE OF SORCERY, CURSES,
AND CURSED OBJECTS TO NON-SORCERERS.
HOWEVER, THIS SHALL NOT APPLY WHEN
IT IS NECESSARY TO FULFILL
THE DUTIES OF THE PREVIOUS ARTICLE.
SECRECY
There are probably curse users among
the participants in the fights, as well.
Do be careful.
Why are we changing?
Hakari-san was expelled for
clashing with the upper brass.
He's also actively violating
jujutsu regulations.
If he finds out we're with
Jujutsu High, he might run.
It's like we're cops and he's the robber.
Hmm?
We're on Jujutsu High's side now?
We're in a gray zone,
but in Hakari-san's eyes,
at least, we're with them.
Is he likely to cooperate
with us in the first place?
I'm not sure.
All our senpai say he's
a good-for-nothing,
but Okkotsu-senpai claimed
he's stronger than him.
We definitely want his strength.
Go home, brats.
This isn't a place for you to hang out.
You have until the count
of three to turn around.
Any other choices will
earn a beating from me.
We need money.
Let us enter the fights held here.
The first rule is:
You do not talk about the fight club.
Now answer me. Who told you?
You'll get your beating after that.
I don't know his name.
I killed him.
It was about a month ago.
He was some scumbag who was all talk.
Kondo disappeared about a month ago.
I'll fill his slot for you.
Or would you rather I lay you
out in front of the bookie?
Oh, yeah. He'd be wary if we
suddenly asked to see him.
I guess we shouldn't know
his name's Hakari, either.
Yes.
No, there's no proof.
Time to zip the lips.
Are you sure?
That's enough.
The boss has given you the go-ahead.
We'll pit you against
today's seeded fighter.
However...
he's the one fighting.
That's good for us.
Itadori's better suited to the fighting.
No go. I'll fight.
Boss said he doesn't like you.
Boss
If you don't like it, the deal's off.
Fine. We'll take it, then.
Fushiguro, that was risky.
Your bluffs went too far.
That's not actually true.
If curse users are participating too,
that means there must be decent turnover.
More importantly...
Yeah, they're here.
If he was watching us
through security cameras,
there's a high chance
Hakari-senpai is in here.
Itadori, you snoop around
from the inside.
I'll snoop around that parking
lot in the meantime.
Maybe.
Maybe?
He's probably leaving me
to my own devices.
If he learns we're infiltrating his club,
we'll lose his trust and our opportunity
to make contact with Hakari-san.
Well, we'll just resort to
force if that happens.
That's really our last resort.
We're only here to ask Hakari-san
for his cooperation.
I'd like to avoid anything that'll
affect our future relations.
To be honest, I don't think I
should be doing anything tonight.
But I don't want to waste the time
we have until Tsumiki is required
to declare her participation
in the Culling Game.
Right now...
it's 5 PM on the 10th.
So nine days until the deadline, huh?
It took longer to get
here than we thought.
That's why I'll be trying to
look for Hakari-san tonight,
but if it looks risky, I'll pull out.
That's why I say "maybe."
Got it.
There are only two rules.
No running away,
and no using cursed techniques.
How come?
I don't mind if they're
using cursed techniques.
Because most of the spectators
are non-sorcerers,
those who can't see them.
A fight people can't see
won't excite them.
And the "no running" rule?
It means you fight where
the spectators can see you.
It's all about the spectators, huh?
Of course.
This is a business.
What's the boss like?
You curious?
Well, yeah.
You'll know if you meet him.
Can I meet him?
There are two kinds of matches.
Real beat-downs, like in today's
tournament, and fixed bouts.
The boss writes the script for those.
He might call for you if you
manage to shine out there.
In other words, I just need
to put on a good show.
That makes things simple.
That's your opponent.
I was blown away the first
time I saw him, too.
Yeah.
It's really all about
drawing in the crowd.
Now, we're getting started again tonight!
It's time for the
Gachinko Fight Club Tournament!
Commentary will be provided by me,
your very own John☆Bobby!
Allow me to introduce tonight's
exciting match-up!
We're joined by a sudden upstart!
Will he rise up or burn out?!
It's the Dangerous Fireball Kid,
Yuji Itadori!
He stands like a panda, sits like
a panda, and walks like a panda!
It's Panda!
Fighting Arena
2nd Floor CH 6
Now, place your bets, place your bets!
Everyone ready?!
Let's get ready to rumble!
I can feel my passion draining away.
What's wrong, Kin-chan?
Luck is meant to be tested, you know.
It's boring to gamble when you
know who'll win from the start.
There aren't many stray sorcerers
who are tough enough to beat Panda.
Whoa!
This is the best bout in my
career as a commentator!
Looks like you might be wrong.
Huh?
Fighting Arena
2nd Floor CH 6
Have you been able to see Hakari-senpai?
No.
Tap
He's not wary of me since
we know each other,
but he's avoiding me.
Tap Tap Tap Tap
Roooar
The other third-year's
technique is also a problem.
You're hiding the fact that you're
from Jujutsu High, right?
Yeah.
Good, good.
You know what to do now, right?
Whoa!
This is definitely the best bout
in my career as a commentator!
Though I've only been one for two weeks!
Tap
Tap Tap Tap
The winner: Itadori!
What a punch!
I can't move!
The SPCA won't stand for this!
Your acting sucks.
Send Itadori up to the roof
when the tournament's over.
Huh?
He's sure to win it.
Plus, he's intentionally
fighting in three dimensions
to wow the spectators on the upper floors.
I can write a good script with him.
And like I always say,
strike while the iron's hot.
That's so dumb. Cut it out.
Got it. And what about the other brat?
Continue to be vigilant.
I'll send Kirara for
extra security later.
Huh?
I'm feeling a nice buzz now.
I haven't felt this alive since
my ex maxed out my credit cards.
Quit bringing up your ex.
Jujutsu High Third-Year, Kinji Hakari
Jujutsu High Third-Year,  Kirara Hoshi
I see.
It sounds like Itadori's going
to be able to contact Hakari.
Why haven't you been able to
see him yet, Panda-senpai?
Well, I do know where he is.
In the monitor room on the roof.
But I can't get close.
You can't get close?
Even when I approach the door,
I can't close the distance.
The sensation feels similar
to Satoru's technique.
It's probably due to Kirara's technique.
Kirara?
But the other third-year was a guy, right?
Yeah.
So does that phenomenon only occur
when Kirara-san's in the monitor room?
I don't know.
I focused on being a circus panda instead
of pushing too far and making them run off.
I'm glad you two showed up.
Do you think Itadori will
succeed in persuading him?
It'll be tough,
but I think it's just a matter of time.
Itadori's bright, charming personality
is a good match for Hakari.
But he sucks at lying, doesn't he?
He doesn't just suck at it.
He struggles to even see
lying as an option.
So once Itadori enters
the monitor room,
I'll take control of the
place quickly and quietly
so I can buy time for the
two of them to talk.
No, that's not...
It'll be fine.
I'll just put them to sleep.
I know where the cameras
and their blind spots are.
How many guards are there?
Four at the entrance,
and two on each floor except the roof.
We can handle that.
The only real concern is
Kirara-san's technique.
We can't do anything about that now.
If they can warp Itadori out
of there or warp in backup,
we'll give up on persuading Hakari.
You're still a first-year, Yu-chan?
You're young.
"Yu-chan"?
Kin-chan had to repeat
a year in middle school.
You sound happy.
Well, yeah.
It's been a while since
Kin-chan's gotten heated up.
You see, I love it when
Kin-chan is passionate.
Itadori.
Would you believe me if I said
you can earn a million yen a month by
doing something for just one hour a day?
Huh?
Hmm?
Depends on what that "something" is.
But you'll have to pay me 200,000 yen
to buy the information on
what that "something" is.
Huh?
I don't believe you, then.
Good. Like you suspected,
that's a classic con.
The swindler pretends to be rich
and sells the means to becoming rich
to scam money from others.
It's obvious if you
think about it logically,
but there's a stupid amount
of fools who fall for it.
Why?
It's all because of passion.
Passion?
Both the swindler and the deceived
have the same passionate drive
to change their lives.
People high on passion lose
sight of their judgment.
Yet no one can fall in love
without passion, either.
I love that passion.
Do you know the most direct way
for people to deal with passion?
Gambling?
I knew you would get it.
Life is a gamble.
Loads of women have dumped me
because they hate gambling,
but they've got it wrong.
Our society throws out
those who can't bet big
and those who don't know when to fold.
There isn't a single person
who doesn't gamble.
What people hate isn't the gambling,
it's losing and being ruined.
Aren't there people who just want
to live a peaceful life, too?
I don't know anyone like that.
I love passion.
Passion is gambling,
and gambling is life.
And love is control.
In the future, I want to control this
nation's passion through my fight club.
With the existence of curses going public
and headquarters barely able to function,
this is my chance to expand the business.
I'm going to crush the
obstacles before me
and make them publicly recognize
my fight club in the coming revisions
to the jujutsu regulations.
At any rate, I'll need a
strong piece on the board.
Itadori...
Want to get high on my passion?
Boss, I need to—
Itadori, want something to drink?
Oh, I'm good with anything.
Other than liquor.
What, can't handle it?
That's not the issue. I'm still underage.
You don't strike me as the
type to care about that.
Did you know Satoru Gojo
can't hold his liquor, either?
Really? Who's Gojo?
And I never said I couldn't.
Look.
Huh?
There isn't a single sorcerer who
doesn't know of Satoru Gojo.
So why did you feign ignorance?
Were you...
sent by Jujutsu High?
Listen! I—
H-Hey!
L-Lis—
When I get a call from Kirara's number,
it's a signal something's up.
Listen to me!
Hell no!
My passion's gone cold now!
Episode 52
Passion
If we can convince them,
negotiations with Hakari-san
will go more smoothly!
Wait, Kirara!
Stay out of this!
You have to show me!
Right here and now!
Please! There's no time!
Kin-chan's in danger!
Next Episode
Cog